Guide to the Center for International Policy Records, 1960-2016 and undated; 1960-ongoing RL.00205
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Selig Harrison Papers, 1960-2011 and undated
  - Geographic Subseries, 1960-2011 and undated
    - Agricultural modernization, Geneva United Nations Development Programme (UNDP), Nort Korea, 1998 (Box 68)
    - Agriculture, North Korea, 1993-2008 and undated (Box 68)
    - Air balance, North Korea, 1986-2000 (Box 68)
    - Amphetamines and arms trade, North Korea, 2003 (Box 68)
    - Army and base power, North Korea, 1997 (Box 68)
    - Articles for North Korea trip, 2009 (Box 68)
    - Bonn prime speech, North Korea, 2005 and undated (Box 68)
    - Book introduction prime, North Korea - George Bernard Shaw story, "mouse that roared" software, 1999 and undated (Box 68)
    - Booster phase option, North Korea, 1999-2000 (Box 68)
    - Changes in North Korea as revealed in the testimonies of Saetomins, Korea Institute for National Unification (KINU), 2008 (Box 68)
    - Children's tales, Pyongyang - A Tale of Two Generals, 1989 and A Winged Horse, 1989 (Box 68)
    - Central Intelligence Agency assessments on North Korea missile threat, 1998-2000 (Box 68)
    - Central Intelligence Agency and North Korea, undated (Box 68)
    - Collapse secondary, North Korea, 1994-2008 and undated (Box 68)
    - Compromise and arms control, North Korea, update 1994 (Box 68)
    - Constitutional changes, North Korea, 1998 (Box 68)
    - Conventional forces issue, North Korea, 2003 and undated (Box 68)
    - Debt, North Korea, 1988-1997 and undated (Box 68)
    - "Defense Policy of an Alienated State," Denny Roy, 1991-1998 and undated (Box 68)
      North Korea.
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea arms control start with Selig Harrison and Kim Il Sung, 1990-1991 and undated (Box 68)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea briefing book, policy areas: multilateral talks, terrorism, 2004 (Box 68)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea contacts, 1998-2003 and undated (Box 68)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea economy opening, 1986-1997 (Box 68)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea in 2002, including Bush, Axis of Evil (Box 68)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea terrorism, 2008 and undated (Box 68)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea trip, 1994 June (Box 68)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea-United States relations and Untied States policy on North Korea, 1981-2008 and undated, 1 of 3 (Box 68)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea-United States relations and United States policy on North Korea, 1981-2008 and undated, 2 of 3 folders (Box 69)
    - Detained journalists in Democratic People's Republic of Korea, 2009 (Box 69)
    - Development Cooperation reports, Democratic People's Republic of Korea, 1992-1994 (Box 69)
    - Economic reforms, North Korea, 2004-2006 (Box 69)
    - Economic sanctions, North Korea, 2006 (Box 69)
    - Economy (general) and economic reforms, North Korea, 1985-2006 and undated, 3 folders (Box 69)
    - Food crisis and aid, North Korea, 1997-2005 and undated, 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Foreign trade, North Korea, 1992-1996 and undated (Box 70)
    - General, North Korea, including Seligh S. Harrison pieces, 1999-2010 and undated, 3 folders (Box 70)
    - Glasek and Levy on financial sanctions, North Korea, 2007 (Box 70)
    - Hankyoreh, North Korea, 2010 and undated (Box 70)
    - Helicopter incident (starts with United States Demilitarized Zone military contacts), 1994-1995 (Box 70)
    - Human rights, North Korea, 2001-2005 and undated, 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Hwang Jang-yop, 1992-1998 (Box 70)
    - Hwang Jang-yop on comparison between Kim Jung-il and Kim Il-sung, 1998 and undated (Box 70)
    - Information technology revolution, North Korea, 2000 (Box 71)
    - Internal politics, North Korea, 1994-2009 (Box 71)
    - International politics, North Korea, Hawks versus Doves and Woolsey, 1988-2002 (Box 71)
    - News articles for North Korea visit, 2005 Apr. 9 (Box 71)
    - The North Korean Economy, Marcus Noland, 1996 (Box 71)
    - Japan-Democratic People's Republic of Korea, 1989-1999 (Box 71)
    - Kim Il-sung, 1989 and undated (Box 71)
    - Kim Il-sung - Christian roots, 1989-1996 (Box 71)
    - Kim Il-sung's North Korea - declassified, undated, 2 folders (Box 71)
    - Kim Jong-il, 1994-2004 and undated (Box 71)
    - Kim Jong-il changes in image, 2000 (Box 71)
    - Kim Jong-il and military, 2000 and undated (Box 71)
    - Kim Jong Un, 2010 (Box 71)
    - Letters to Pyongyang, 1995-2000 (Box 71)
    - Marcus, George - correspondence regarding North Korea trip, 2008 (Box 71)
    - Military in economy, North Korea, 1983-1998 (Box 71)
    - Minimum conditions for humanitarian action in the Democratic People's Republic of Korea, 2001 (Box 71)
    - Missile launch, North Korea, 2006 July (Box 71)
    - Money laundering, North Korea, 2003 (Box 72)
    - Muskgrove conference on North Korea, pre-reading, 2004 May 14-18 (Box 72)
    - Muskgrove meeting, 2004 Nov. 4 (Box 72)
    - Names and letters, 1995-2000 (Box 72)
    - New Democratic People's Republic of Korea constitution, 1998 and undated (Box 72)
    - North Korea Human Rights Act and North Korea Freedom Act, 2003 and 2004 (Box 72)
    - North Korean missile launch and post-Supreme People's Assembly power reshuffle, 2009 (Box 72)
    - North Korea pieces, Selig S. Harrison, 2009 and undated (Box 72)
    - North Korea power structure, undated (Box 72)
    - North Korean press coverage with mentions of Selig Harrison, 2006-2009 (Box 72)
    - North Korean reforms and Heidi Brown, 2005 (Box 72)
    - North Korea sanctions - questions, 2005-2006 and undated (Box 72)
    - North Korean scientific exchanges - Rick Stone, 2004 (Box 72)
    - North Korea trip, 2005 (Box 72)
    - Obama and North Korea, 2008-2009 (Box 72)
    - Ok, Li nam, 1997-1998 and undated (Box 72)
    - Olympics, including Rungra Island visit and Kwangbok department store, 1987 (Box 72)
    - Oxford Analytica regarding North Korea, 2004 and undated (Box 72)
    - Pamphlets, Pyongyang - new buildings of the Workers' Party Era, 1987, Pyongyang metro, 1980, Chang gwang-won health complex, 1981 (Box 73)
    - Population, North Korea, 1991-1997 (Box 73)
    - "Possible Areas of Cooperation with the Democratic People's Republic of Korea," binder, 2003 (Box 73)
    - Preemptive strike and forward defense, North Korea, 1994 and undated (Box 73)
    - Prime United States officials, North Korea, 2003-2005 and undated (Box 73)
    - Pyongyang, 1995-2004 and undated (Box 73)
    - Pyongyang/Beijing trip, 2008-2009 (Box 73)
    - Pyongyang devastation (Korean War), 1991-1992 and undated (Box 73)
    - Pyongyang trip, 1992, 1994 and 1998 (Box 73)
    - Rajin-sonbong, 1993-1996 (Box 73)
    - Recommendations, North Korea, 1992-2000 (Box 73)
    - Reform by stealth, North Korea, 1996-1999 and undated (Box 73)
    - Research collaboration between Kim Chaek University of Technology and Syracuse University, 2003 (Box 73)
    - Restarting Yongbyon (North Korea nuclear plant), 2000-2002 (Box 73)
    - Russia-North Korea rapprochement, 1990-2003 and undated (Box 73)
    - Scenario for absorption and post-collapse - will North Korea collapse? 1995-1998 (Box 73)
    - Shin Sang Ok, 1985-1986 (Box 73)
    - Selig S. Harrison role and visits to North, 1967-1987 and undated (Box 74)
    - Senator Kerry on North Korea, 2004 (Box 74)
    - Spy planes, 2000-2001 and undated (Box 74)
    - Tourism, 1990-1992 and undated (Box 74)
    - Treasury, United States-North Koream 2005-2006 (Box 74)
    - United States companies with sanctions lifted, North Korea, 1995-1999 (Box 74)
    - United States economic engagement with Democratic People's Republic of Korea, 2009 Oct. (Box 74)
    - United States escalation - new war plan, Democratic People's Republic of Korea, 2003-2005 (Box 74)
    - United States Forces - Li-Hyung Chul, Kim Hyung University, 1999 and undated (Box 74)
    - United States Korea task force contacts, including John Lewis, 2004-2005 and undated (Box 74)
    - United States-North Korea contacts, 1999-2004 (Box 74)
    - United States-North Korea Hawks contacts, 1995-2004 and undated (Box 74)
    - United States policy to the Democratic People's Republic of Korea, 1971-1999 (Box 74)
    - United States prisoners of war in the Democratic People's Republic of Korea, 1989 and undated (Box 74)
    - United States sanctions policy on North Korea, 1988-2000, 2 folders (Box 75)
    - Vice Marshal to Myong Rok communique, United States-Korea, 2000 (Box 75)
    - Women and children in the Democratic People's Republic of Korea, 1965-1972 and undated (Box 75)
    - Zylka, William (CIA mission to North Korea), 2000-2004 (Box 75)
    - 2ID brigade deploying from Korea to Iraq, 2004 (Box 76)
    - Arms Control Association, 2002-2006 (Box 76)
    - Asian financial crisis and capital controls, 1997-1999 and undated (Box 76)
    - Axis of Evil (Iraq, Iran, Democratic People's Republic of Korea) (Box 76)
    - Bush policy, including Korea, 2000-2003 (Box 76)
    - China-AfPak, 2009-2010 and undated (Box 76)
    - China-Kashmir, including Gilgit Baltistan, 2007-2010 (Box 76)
    - Cuba, Vietnam, North Korea, 2001-2003 and undated (Box 76)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea-Pakistan, 2 folders (Box 76)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea - terrorism, 1987-1999 (Box 76)
    - European Union security and defense, 2000 (Box 76)
    - Falling dollar, 2004 (Box 76)
    - Foreign investment in North Korea, including by South Korea, 1993-1999 and undated (Box 76)
    - General, inter-regional relations and other, 1994-2006 and undated (Box 76)
    - Gilgit-Baltistan, 2009-2010 and undated (Box 77)
    - Globalization general, undated (Box 77)
    - Hankyoreh - United States economic collapse, 2003-2004 (Box 77)
    - India-China, 2006-2010 (Box 77)
    - Japan-India, 2004 (Box 77)
    - Joint Declaration by the Russian Federation and the People's Republic of China (Beijing, China), 2002 Dec. 2 (Box 77)
    - Kosovo, 1999 (Box 77)
    - Missile threat to United States report, 1998 (Box 77)
    - Nationalism lecture, 1983 and undated (Box 77)
    - North Atlatic Treaty Organization (NATO) first use, secondary, 1998 (Box 77)
    - North Korea-Libya, 2003-2006 (Box 77)
    - Nunn-Lugar model, 1995-2000 (Box 77)
    - National security - general, 2002-2005 (Box 77)
    - Obama and foreign affairs, 2008 (Box 77)
    - Public Relations Campaign for The Government of The Republic of Slovenia, Washington World Group, LTD, 1995-1997 (Box 77)
    - Russia and the Korean Peninsula, 2005-2008 and undated (Box 77)
    - Security overview, 1992-1999 (Box 77)
    - United States dollar, 2004-2005 (Box 77)
    - United States foreign policy - general (Box 77)
    - United States hegemony, 1968-2003 (Box 77)
    - United States in the wake of 9/11, 2002 and undated (Box 77)
    - United States-Russia relations, 2004 (Box 77)
    - Wassenaar Arrangement, 1996 (Box 77)
    - World armament and disarmament, Stockholm International Peace Research Institute (SIPRI) yearbooks, 1972-1997 (Box 77)
  - Nuclear and Energy, 1966-2011 and undated
    Contains files related to nuclear armament and disarmament, especially regarding negotiations to denuclearize the Korean peninsula, arms sales, sanctions, and other nuclear incidents in various regions. Also contains files related to various energy programs, sometimes nuclear but especially regarding oil and gas resources in Russia and Northeast Asia, and energy development programs and proposals in this region. Files are organized alphabetically by name. Some materials have been removed to the Professional Subseries.
    - Administrative, including regarding workshops, 2001-2004 (Box 78)
    - Asia letters, Department of Energy, 2001-2002 and undated (Box 78)
    - Beijing meeting, 2001 (Box 78)
    - Beijing prime, 2001-2004 (Box 78)
    - Beijing trip, general, 2004 (Box 78)
    - Beijing workshop prime, 2003 (Box 78)
    - Building Nuclear Confidence in the Korean Peninsula, workshop proceedings, 2001 July 23-24 (Box 78)
    - Bush policy on the Democratic People's Republic of Korea nuclear program, 2007-2008 (Box 78)
    - Center - oil, 2001-2002 (Box 78)
    - China energy, 1982-2003 (Box 78)
    - China and Japan compete for Russian oil and gas, 2003-2004 (Box 78)
    - China nuclear, 2005 and undated (Box 78)
    - China nuclear - size of arsenal, United States stop threatening, 2005-2006 (Box 78)
    - China nuclear spying flop, 1999 (Box 78)
    - China oil and gas reserves - East China and Yellow Sea, 2002-2004 and undated (Box 78)
    - China-South Asia-Iraq, nuclear, 2004-2008 and undated (Box 78)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea energy, 1996-2005 and undated (Box 78)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea energy needs, 2001-2009 and undated (Box 78)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea nuclear - general, 2000-2010 and undated, 3 folders (Box 79)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea nuclear capability, 2002 (Box 79)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea nuclear testing, 2006-2009 and undated (Box 79)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea oil, 1994-2001 and undated (Box 79)
    - Democratic People's Republic of Korea-United States Agreed Framework, 1999-2004 (Box 79)
    - Department of Energy, 2001-2006 (Box 79)
    - Department of Energy report and administrative records ("Toward Oil and Gas Cooperation in Northeast Asia"), 2003 (Box 80)
    - Did North Korea sell UF6 to Libya? 2005 (Box 80)
    - Disarmament Forum II, India and Pakistan: Peace by Peace, 2004 (Box 80)
    - East China Sea, 2007-2009 (Box 80)
    - East China seabed workshop and China oil contacts, 2003-2006 (Box 80)
    - East China Sea, including maps, 1977-1996 (Box 80)
    - Energy Aid for North Korea: Fossil Fuel Options and Denuclearization, Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars and Korea Energy Economics Institute, 2007 June (Box 80)
    - Energy cooperation in Northeast Asia - proposal, 1998-2002, 3 folders (Box 80)
    - Energy in Northeast Asia - reference general, 1993-1998 (Box 80)
    - Energy pending, 2001 (Box 80)
    - Expansion of seabed for report, 2002 (Box 80)
    - First use - Japan and North Korea, 2009-2010 (Box 81)
    - Five Proposals for the Establishment of a Northeast Asian Development Banks, 2002 Nov. (Box 81)
    - "Forgotten bargain" and contacts, 2000-2007 and undated (Box 81)
    - Funding, 2001-2002 (Box 81)
    - Future of nuclear issue, Korea and South America, 1991-1995 (Box 81)
    - "Gas Pipelines and the North Korean Nuclear Crisis," Asia Pacific Center for Security Studies, 2003 (Box 81)
    - High enrichment uranium (HEU), bulk North Korea and Pakistan, 1983-2007 and undated, 2 folders (Box 81)
    - High enrichment uranium (HEU)follow up prime, 2004-2005 (Box 81)
    - High enrichment uranium (HEU) update - Siegfried Hecker, 2004-2007 (Box 81)
    - History of nuclear issue, Korea, 1991-1997 (Box 81)
    - How to delegitimize first use, 2005-2006 and undated (Box 81)
    - India - list of nuclear facilities, 1998-2006 (Box 81)
    - India - nuclear, 1999-2007 and undated (Box 81)
    - India - nuclear/energy, 1966, 1998-2006 and undated, 4 folders (Box 82)
    - India-United States nuclear missile, including Hyde Act, 2008 (Box 82)
    - Iran - nuclear, 1994, 2001-2008, 1 of 2 (Box 82)
    - Iran - nuclear, 1994, 2001-2008, 2 of 2 (Box 83)
    - International dissatisfaction with United States regarding Article 6, 2005-2006 (Box 83)
    - Japan energy, 1994-2003 and undated (Box 83)
    - Japan - nuclear, 2003-2011 and undated, 2 folders (Box 83)
    - Japan - reference, 2003-2004 (Box 83)
    - Japan-United States nuclear alliance, 1997-2010 (Box 83)
    - Japan uranium enrichment, 2006 (Box 83)
    - Korea Energy Economics Institute co-sponsorship of pipeline workshop, 2009 (Box 83)
    - Khan, A.Q., 1990, 2001-2009 and undated (Box 83)
    - Korea oil names, 2001 and undated (Box 83)
    - Korean Peninsula Energy Development Organization (KEDO) and light water reactors (LWRs), 2005 and undated (Box 84)
    - Korean Peninsula - nuclear, 1992 and undated (Box 84)
    - KoRus pipelines, 2003 and undated (Box 84)
    - Law of Sea, Choon-Ho Park ("reference checked March 25, 2004"), 1975 and undated (Box 84)
    - Letter to Scott and Price, 2001-2003 (Box 84)
    - London Review - nuclear posture piece, 2006-2010 (Box 84)
    - Meijer, Hans - HS International Trading BV (HS), 2001-2002 (Box 84)
    - Middle East nuclear free zone, 2006 (Box 84)
    - Miscellaneous notes and contacts (Box 84)
    - Moscow (Korea oil and gas substantive), 2004 Oct. 21 (Box 84)
    - Moscow trip, 2001 (Box 84)
    - National Academy of Sciences on subcritical testing, 2006 (Box 84)
    - Non-proliferation Bush speech and United States nuclear double standard, 2004 (Box 84)
    - Non-proliferation - general, 2005-2006 (Box 84)
    - Non-proliferation treaty (NPT) in prespective - what countries have given up and why, e.g. South Africa; why countries joined the NPT, 2006 and undated (Box 84)
    - Northeast Asia nuclear free zone, 1992-2006 and undated (Box 84)
    - North Korea nuclear restart, including Yongbyon, 2009-2010 and undated (Box 84)
    - "The North Korean Nuclear Crisis and United States-North Korean Relations" prepared for conference on "The Second Bush Administration and the Korean Peninsula," 2005 Mar. 30-Apr. 1 (Box 84)
    - Nuclear alters strategy and balance, 1976-1999 (Box 84)
    - Nuclear forces - China, India, France, Britain, and the United States, 2005 (Box 84)
    - Nuclear free zones, 2004-2006 (Box 84)
    - Nuclear - general, 2001-2005 and undated (Box 85)
    - Nuclear, including Korean Peninsula Energy Development Organization (KEDO), 1995-2000 and undated (Box 85)
    - "The Nuclear Issue and North Korea's Integration," prepared for "Korean Peninsula Peace Forum," 2004 (Box 85)
    - Nuclear - Pakistan, Saudi Arabia, Iran, 2003-2004 (Box 85)
    - Nuclear reductions proposal, 1994-2008 and undated (Box 85)
    - Nuclear umbrella, Korea, 1988-1994 and undated (Box 85)
    - Obama nuclear posture, 2010 and undated (Box 85)
    - Paik, Keun-Wock, 1999-2001 and undated (Box 85)
    - Pakistan-North Korea high enrichment uranium (HEU), 2002-2005 (Box 85)
    - Panel discussions: "Confrontation or Engagement?: The Case of the Democratic People's Republic of Korea," 2005 and undated (Box 85)
    - Pipelines and faultlines conference, 2003 Oct. 21-23 (Box 85)
    - Proliferation - United States policy, 1988-2006 and undated (Box 85)
    - Proliferation/weapons of mass destruction, undated (Box 85)
    - "The Prospects for Energy Efficiency Improvements in the Democratic People's Republic of Korea: Evaluating and Exploring the Options," 1995 Oct. (Box 85)
    - Regional energy cooperation in Northeast Asia workshop, 2005 (Box 85)
    - Republic of Korea gas needs, including Shell and liquefied natural gas (LNG), 2000 undated (Box 85)
    - Republic of Korea nuclear, 2003-2010 and undated (Box 85)
    - Russia, 2001-2006 and undated (Box 86)
    - Russia-China - pipelines speech, 2003-2004 (Box 86)
    - "Russian Gas, Oil and Electricity and the Energy Future of the Korean Peninsula" workshop, 2009-2010 (Box 86)
    - Russia gas reference, 2002-2003 and undated (Box 86)
    - Russia nuclear role (Democratic People's Republic of Korea), 1998-2004 (Box 86)
    - Russia upgrades nuclear weapons, 2006 (Box 86)
    - Seabed, especially Sino-Japan, 2005 and undated (Box 86)
    - Selig S. Harrison report - requests for revisions of East China Sea workshop papers, 2004 and undated (Box 86)
    - Seoul workshop on North Korea nuclear and energy, 2005-2006 (Box 86)
    - Seoul workshop and news (energy), 2006 Sep. 12-14 (Box 86)
    - Sibera - Pacific Ocean oil, 2005-2007 and undated (Box 86)
    - Six Party talks, 2003-2007 and undated (Box 86)
    - Six Party talks - United States offer, 2004 (Box 87)
    - Southeast Asia nuclear free zones, 1995-2006 and undated (Box 87)
    - South Korea seabed, 1971 and undated (Box 87)
    - South Korea's sea resources, 2001 and undated (Box 87)
    - Strategic Arms Reduction Treaty (START), 2009 and undated (Box 87)
    - Taiwan-Democratic People's Republic of Korea nuclear waste, 1995-1997 (Box 87)
    - Test ban and fissile cut off, undated (Box 87)
    - Tokyo energy, 2001 and undated (Box 87)
    - "Towards a World Free of Nuclear Weapons" India conference, 2008 and undated (Box 87)
    - Tri-lateral/Beijing talks, 1997-2005 and undated (Box 87)
    - United Nations Resolution 1874 (full-text), 2009 (Box 87)
    - United States-Japan Foundation, 2000 (Box 87)
    - United States nuclear doctrine, 2005 (Box 87)
    - United States nuclear policy and strategy, 1999-2004 and undated (Box 87)
    - United States - size of nuclear arsenals, 2006 (Box 87)
    - United States upgrades nuclear arsenal, 2005-2006 (Box 87)
    - Uranium prime, North Korea, 2003-2009 and undated (Box 87)
    - Wilson Center, 1997-2002 and undated (Box 87)
    - Workshop papers, 2003-2004 (Box 87)
    - Workshop report notes, undated (Box 87)
    - Yellow Sea workshop, 2003-2004 (Box 87)
  - Professional Subseries, 1991-2010 and undated
    Contains correspondence and other documentation regarding Harrison's submissions and publications with various media outlets, including his source material, speeches delivered at workshops and other events on various subjects, documentation of the organization and attendance of professional workshops, published pieces, and other general professional records related to the Center for International Policy, the Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars, and the Century Foundation. Files are organized alphabetically by name. More speeches and manuscripts can be found in the Geographic and Nuclear and Energy subseries.
    - ABC regarding Democratic People's Republic of Korea, 2003-2007 and undated (Box 88)
    - Asia speeches, undated (Box 88)
    - BBC and World News regarding Korea, Pakistan and Afghanistan, 1995-2010 and undated (Box 88)
    - Boston Globe regarding Pakistan, etc., 2003, 2007 (Box 88)
    - CBC regarding Korean Peninsula, 1993-2005 and undated (Box 88)
    - CBS - Peter Klein regarding North Korea and Syria, 2006-2007 (Box 88)
    - Center for International Policy Asia Program/general, 2002 (Box 88)
    - Center for International Policy - emails to task force on media impact, 2002-2003 (Box 88)
    - Center for International Policy - proposals, grants and awards, 2002-2003 (Box 88)
    - China-Taiwan-United States speech, undated (Box 88)
    - Columbus speech, North Korea, undated (Box 88)
    - Correspondence - "Jed," 1942-1943 and undated (Box 88)
    - Correspondence - miscellaneous, 1999-2010 (Box 88)
    - D.C. articles, 2007-2008 (Box 88)
    - Expense account workshop records, 2006 (Box 88)
    - Financial Times regarding North Korea Uranium, China, Pakistan, India and Kashmir, 2002-2007 and undated (Box 88)
    - Foreign Affairs regarding North Korea, India and Iran, 2000-2006 (Box 88)
    - Foreign Exchange regarding North Korea, 2006-2007 (Box 88)
    - Globalization speech, undated (Box 88)
    - Gloucester speech on North Korea nuclear and Al Queda, undated (Box 88)
    - Hankyoreh articles, 1999-2001 and undated, 2 folders (Box 88)
    - Hankyoreh Future, 2003-2004 (Box 88)
    - Hankyoreh - Korea angle, undated (Box 88)
    - Hankyoreh - past articles, 1997-1998 and undated (Box 89)
    - Hankyoreh - past articles, 2001-2005 and undated (Box 89)
    - Hankyoreh - past articles, 2003-2004 and undated (Box 89)
    - Hanyoreh - Port Nou and impact on foreign policy, 2006 (Box 89)
    - Herald Tribune, 1999-2009 and undated (Box 89)
    - Japan speeches, undated (Box 89)
    - Jimmy Carter, 2002 and undated (Box 89)